<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Busenur Kizilaslan Personal Web Page</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Busenur Kizilaslan Personal Web Page</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Blog</title>
      <link>/blog/post1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/post1/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>I am a research assistant at the Department of Statistics, Marmara University, Turkey. In 2020, I obtained my PhD degree from Yıldız Technical University’s Department of Statistics, under the direction of Erol Eğrioğlu and Atif Evren, and I received my master and bachelor degrees from Mimar Sinan Fine Arts University, Department of Statistics, under the direction of Erol Eğrioğlu and Barış Aşıkgil.
In 2018, I won the second prize of Young Scientists Awards by presenting a part of my dissertation at International Conference on Trends and Perspectives in Linear Statistical Inference (LinStat) in Poland.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>News</title>
      <link>/news/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/</guid>
      <description>   Jun 3, 2022 Participating in NordStar Workshop Oslo  May 24, 2022 Participating in Ethical AI in Practice Oslo    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/publications/</guid>
      <description>Article Kizilaslan, B., Egrioglu, E., &amp;amp; Evren, A. A. (2020). Intuitionistic fuzzy ridge regression functions. Communications in Statistics-Simulation and Computation, 49(3), 699-708.
 Sarıca, B., Eğrioğlu, E., &amp;amp; Aşıkgil, B. (2018). A new hybrid method for time series forecasting: AR–ANFIS. Neural Computing and Applications, 29(3), 749-760.
 Inan, D., Egrioglu, E., Sarica, B., Askin, O. E., &amp;amp; Tez, M. (2017). Particle swarm optimization based Liu-type estimator. Communications in Statistics-Theory and Methods, 46(22), 11358-11369.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
